<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<source>
    <job>
        <title>Business Development Executive</title>
        <date>2024-09-16</date>
        <referencenumber>ODI-23414</referencenumber>
        <url>https://my.odiware.com/jobs</url>
        <company>Odiware Technologies</company>
        <location>Bhubaneshwar, India</location>
        <description><![CDATA[<p data-last-history-steps="260597223298089">Business Development Executive - ERP<br></p><p data-last-history-steps="260597223298089"><strong>Role Description</strong></p><p>This is a full-time on-site role for a Business Development Executive at Odiware Technologies in Bhubaneswar. The role involves tasks such as new business development, lead generation, business communication, and account management on a day-to-day basis.</p><p><strong>Key Responsibilities</strong></p><p>• Identify and develop new business opportunities for ERP implementation services.</p><p>• Build and maintain strong relationships with clients, understanding their business needs and offering tailored solutions.</p><p>• Conduct market research to identify potential clients and industry trends.</p><p>• Present and demonstrate Odoo ERP solutions to prospective clients.</p><p>• Prepare and deliver compelling proposals and presentations.</p><p>• Collaborate with the technical team to ensure successful project delivery.</p><p>• Negotiate contracts and close sales deals.</p><p>• Meet and exceed sales targets and KPIs.</p><p>• Attend industry events and networking opportunities to promote the company’s services.</p><p>• Provide regular reports on sales activities, pipeline, and forecasts.&nbsp;</p><p><strong>Qualifications</strong></p><p>• Bachelor’s degree in Business Administration, Marketing, IT, or a related field.</p><p>• Proven experience in business development, sales, or account management, preferably in the software industry.</p><p>• Strong knowledge of Odoo applications or other ERP applications is a must.</p><p>• Excellent communication, presentation, and negotiation skills.</p><p>• Ability to understand and articulate complex software solutions to clients.</p><p>• Self-motivated with a strong work ethic and the ability to work independently.</p><p>• Proficient in CRM tools and Microsoft Office Suite.</p><p>• Willingness to travel as needed.&nbsp;</p><p>Job Type: Full-time&nbsp;</p><p><strong>Schedule</strong></p><p>• Day shift&nbsp;</p><p><strong>Supplemental Pay</strong></p><p>• Commission pay&nbsp;</p><p><strong>Experience</strong></p><p>• Business development: 1 year (Preferred)</p><p>• Odoo or ERP Solutions Business Development: 1 year (Required)</p><p>

<br></p>]]></description>
        <salary>Not Disclosed</salary>
    </job>
</source>
